{
    "id": "272e6de588934fa4ba1a78d80ef0c332",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Honey is ………………………. than milk.",
            "description": "Most adjectives of one syllable form the comparative by adding –er and superlative by adding –est to the positive.",
            "answers": [
                "sweeter",
                "more sweet",
                "more sweeter"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ebd6022b1b3749519af5f027b28a174e"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………………… than that.",
            "description": "Better is the comparative form of good.",
            "answers": [
                "more good",
                "gooder",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ddd0ac5d449b4c0194c2fbc1d422b042"
        },
        {
            "question": "We played well but they played even ………………………….",
            "description": "Better is the comparative of well.",
            "answers": [
                "more well",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8d7a205d4cd43159b8946e530e06743"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was …………………………..than her husband.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more kind",
                "kinder",
                "more kinder"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8eb1227d5f224a6388712ebdb62e7862"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………………. than that.",
            "description": "Most adjectives of one syllable form the comparative by adding –er and superlative by adding –est.",
            "answers": [
                "white",
                "more white",
                "whiter"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58b4f063c505498799ad1838f95e0d55"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was the ………………………….. of all men.",
            "description": "Noblest is the superlative form of noble.",
            "answers": [
                "most noble",
                "most noblest",
                "noblest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8ff7feee330d431a973d9193a1b3e53d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rana is ……………………….. than his brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wealthy",
                "more wealthy",
                "wealthier"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c18f9bf698134c51abf765f31ed0b717"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the ………………………… day of his life.",
            "description": "When the positive of a one syllable adjective ends in a consonant and that consonant is preceded by a short vowel, the consonant is doubled before adding –er and –est.",
            "answers": [
                "most sad",
                "most saddest",
                "saddest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "34557af4a27247b5af17faa8276c7c97"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………….. than his colleagues.",
            "description": "Adjectives of more than two syllables form the comparative by adding more.",
            "answers": [
                "industrious",
                "more industrious",
                "most industrious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc502501736c4082bd3af626e8403e28"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………………. than her brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more brave",
                "braver",
                "more braver"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8de2bbe5e5a44cdfb0170368bc7b61b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The new hall is ………………………… than the old one.",
            "description": "Adjectives of more than two syllables form the comparative by adding -more",
            "answers": [
                "splendid",
                "more splendid",
                "splendider"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ecba75803ec4300bdbd634aef84f8b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam was …………………………. than I thought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more easy",
                "easier",
                "more easier"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "725e7f6f533c48a18c5ffb9059bb476f"
        }
    ]
}